(Tan Group Flagship Store Building Collapse Incident Report)
( تقرير حادثة انهيار مبنى المتجر الرئيسي لمجموعة تان )
(Eight years ago.)
(قبل ثماني سنوات.)
(It happened at the exact time my father died.)
(حدث ذلك في نفس الوقت الذي توفي فيه والدي.)
(And Tan Group never disclosed this incident to the public.)
(ولم تكشف مجموعة تان عن هذا الحادث للجمهور قط.)
(All news, reports, and records)
(جميع الأخبار والتقارير والسجلات)
(were deliberately erased.)
(تم محوها عمداً.)
(Not even in the shareholders' meeting archives is there any trace of it.)
(حتى في أرشيف اجتماعات المساهمين لا يوجد أي أثر لذلك.)
(What exactly were they trying to hide?)
(ما الذي كانوا يحاولون إخفاءه بالضبط؟)
Help me look into something.
ساعدني في البحث في أمر ما.
The Tan Group flagship store collapse from eight years ago.
انهيار المتجر الرئيسي لمجموعة تان قبل ثماني سنوات.
You're still up this late?
ما زلت مستيقظاً في هذا الوقت المتأخر؟
If you run into any trouble,
إذا واجهت أي مشكلة،
you should tell me.
يجب أن تخبرني.
As long as you speak up,
طالما أنك تتحدث بصراحة،
I'll do everything I can for you.
سأفعل كل ما بوسعي من أجلك.
Then wire me some money.
ثم أرسل لي بعض المال.
Let's start with
لنبدأ بـ
ten billion.
عشرة مليارات.
I'm joking.
أنا أمزح.
Didn't realize you were that rich.
لم أكن أعلم أنك بهذه الثراء.
Don't work yourself too hard lately.
لا تجهد نفسك كثيراً في الآونة الأخيرة.
Get some rest.
خذ قسطاً من الراحة.
(Liang Yusheng, I found the former flagship store manager)
(ليانغ يوشنغ، لقد وجدت مدير المتجر الرئيسي السابق)
Who is it?
من هذا؟
(I found the former flagship store manager.)
(لقد وجدت مدير المتجر الرئيسي السابق.)
Little boy.
صبي صغير.
=Secret By My Name=
=سر باسمي=
(Adapted from the novel Hotpot Loves Tangyuan by Ye Yijian)
(مقتبس من رواية "هوت بوت يعشق تانغ يوان" للكاتبة يي ييجيان)
=Episode 11=
=الحلقة 11=
Long time no see, Uncle Zhao.
لم أرك منذ مدة طويلة يا عم تشاو.
Do you remember me?
هل تتذكرني؟
I'm Li Zhengzhi's daughter.
أنا ابنة لي Zhengzhi.
I don't know you.
أنا لا أعرفك.
Leave now.
غادر الآن.
Uncle Zhao.
العم تشاو.
I came today to hear a story.
جئت اليوم لأستمع إلى قصة.
Do you still remember, eight years ago,
هل ما زلت تتذكر، قبل ثماني سنوات،
the Tan Group flagship store collapse?
هل انهار المتجر الرئيسي لمجموعة تان؟
A lot of people died in that accident.
لقد لقي الكثير من الناس حتفهم في ذلك الحادث.
Don't push me.
لا تدفعني.
Leave. Now.
ارحل. الآن.
What are you trying to do, Uncle Zhao?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل يا عم تشاو؟
Send me to meet my father?
أرسلني لمقابلة والدي؟
You remember this photo, don't you?
أتذكر هذه الصورة، أليس كذلك؟
Aren't they all your friends?
أليسوا جميعاً أصدقاءك؟
Uncle Zhao,
العم تشاو،
if you want to live in peace,
إذا كنت تريد أن تعيش بسلام،
don't carry debts on your back.
لا تحمل الديون على ظهرك.
(Dad.)
(أب.)
(I'm about to clear your name.)
(سأقوم بتبرئة ساحتك الآن.)
Tan Jianfei, stop right there!
تان جيانفي، توقف هنا!
Tan Jianfei!
تان جيانفي!
Give it back to me!
أعده لي!
Let go of me!
اتركني!
You call this your secret?
أتسمي هذا سرك؟
Tan Jianfei. (Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org)
تان جيانفي. (مسؤول الدعم، شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org)
Do you have any idea
هل لديك أي فكرة؟
how much it took for me
كم استغرق الأمر مني
to get this evidence?
للحصول على هذه الأدلة؟
Shujing.
شوجينغ.
So as long as someone stands in the way of your revenge,
طالما أن هناك من يقف في طريق انتقامك،
you'll kick them aside without hesitation?
هل ستطردهم جانباً دون تردد؟
I was the fool.
كنتُ الأحمق.
For ever trusting someone with the surname Tan.
لثقتي الدائمة بشخص يحمل لقب تان.
Tan Jianfei.
تان جيانفي.
Don't make me hate you even more.
لا تجعلني أكرهك أكثر.
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪An ending that can never be undone♪
♪نهاية لا يمكن التراجع عنها♪
♪Disrupting the old rhythm, laying traps♪
♪إفساد الإيقاع القديم، ونصب الفخاخ♪
♪A board full of snares♪
♪لوح مليء بالطبول♪
♪Carving the past into every smile and word♪
♪ننقش الماضي في كل ابتسامة وكلمة♪
♪After falling, still searching for♪
♪بعد السقوط، ما زلت أبحث♪
♪The old marks♪
♪العلامات القديمة♪
♪Pages filled with attempts to hide the past♪
♪صفحات مليئة بمحاولات إخفاء الماضي♪
♪The next page♪
♪الصفحة التالية♪
♪Is turned, revealing this land of right and wrong♪
♪تتحول، كاشفةً عن هذه الأرض التي فيها الحق والباطل♪
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
Have you had enough of pretending devotion?
هل سئمت من التظاهر بالإخلاص؟
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪The way I came♪
♪الطريقة التي أتيت بها♪
(Liang Yusheng)
(ليانغ يوشينغ)
Shujing.
شوجينغ.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Go to Zhao Youcai's place
اذهب إلى مكان Zhao Youcai
and his shop, search again.
وابحث عن متجره مرة أخرى.
See if there's any backup of the videotapes.
تحقق مما إذا كان هناك أي نسخة احتياطية من أشرطة الفيديو.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll arrange it right away.
سأرتب الأمر على الفور.
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪An ending that can never be undone♪
♪نهاية لا يمكن التراجع عنها♪
♪Disrupting the old rhythm, laying traps♪
♪إفساد الإيقاع القديم، ونصب الفخاخ♪
♪A board full of snares♪
♪لوح مليء بالطبول♪
♪Carving the past into every smile and word♪
♪ننقش الماضي في كل ابتسامة وكلمة♪
♪After falling, still searching for♪
♪بعد السقوط، ما زلت أبحث♪
♪The old marks♪
♪العلامات القديمة♪
♪Pages filled with attempts to hide the past♪
♪صفحات مليئة بمحاولات إخفاء الماضي♪
♪The next page♪
♪الصفحة التالية♪
♪Is turned, revealing this land of right and wrong♪
♪تتحول، كاشفةً عن هذه الأرض التي فيها الحق والباطل♪
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪The way I came♪
♪الطريقة التي أتيت بها♪